Jun Xing (邢骏)

Researcher, miHoYo (米哈游)

http://junxnui.github.io/

junxnui@gmail.com

RESEARCH

My research combines modern concepts in computer graphics, computer vision, machine learning and human computer interaction, with broad applications in 2D/3D/VR/Animation contents authoring, analysis, and synthesis. I am interested in designing interactive/predictive systems and deep learning-based algorithms to free the artists from the tedious works so they can focus on creation.

EDUCATION

University of Hong Kong	2012.09-2016.12
PhD in computer science, advised by Dr. Li-Yi Wei	
University of Science and Technology of China (USTC)	2008.09 - 2012.06
Bachelor in Electronic Engineering and Information	

V

WORK EXPERIENCE	
miHoYo (米哈游)	2019.01 — ongoing
Senior research scientist, Shanghai	
USC Institute for Creative Technologies	2017.05 — 2019.01
Postdoctoral researcher, supervised by Hao Li, Vision and Graphic	es Lab, Los Angeles
Adobe Research	2016.07 — 2016.09
Graphics research intern, Procedural Imaging Group, San Jose	
Autodesk Research	2016.01 — 2016.04
HCI Graphics research intern, UI Graphics Group, Toronto	
Microsoft Research Asia	2014.12-2015.04
Graphics research intern, Visual Computing Group, Beijing	

PUBLICATIONS

[17] Intuitive, Interactive Beard and Hair Synthesis with Generative Models

Kyle Olszewski, Duygu Ceylan, Jun Xing, Jose I. Echevarria, Zhili Chen, Weikai Chen, Hao Li CVPR 2020

[16] Learning Formation of Physically-based Face Attributes

Ruilong Li, Kalle Bladin, Yajie Zhao, Chinmay Chinara, Owen Ingraham, Pengda Xiang, Xinglei Ren, Pratusha Prasad, Biping Kishore, Jun Xing, Hao Li CVPR 2020

[15] Deep Face Normalization

Koki Nagano, Jaewoo Seo, Huiwen Luo, Zejian Wang, *Jun Xing*, Liwen Hu, Lingyu Wei, Hao Li *SIGGRAPH Asia 2019*

[14] Learning Perspective Undistortion of Portraits

Yajie Zhao, Zeng Huang, Tianye Li, Weikai Chen, Chloe LeGendre, Xinglei Ren, *Jun Xing*, Ari Shapiro, Hao Li *ICCV 2019 (Oral)*

[13] HairBrush for Immersive Data-Driven Hair Modeling

Jun Xing, Koki Nagano, Weikai Chen, Haotian Xu, Li-Yi Wei, Yajie Zhao, Jingwan Lu, Byungmoon Kim, Hao Li UIST 2019

[12] Quantization Network

Jiwei Yang, Xu Shen, *Jun Xing*, Xinmei Tian, Houqiang Li, Bing Deng, Jianqiang Huang, Xiansheng Hua *CVPR 2019*

[11] Mask-off: Synthesizing Face Images in the Presence of Head-mounted Displays

Yajie Zhao, Qingguo Xu, Weikai Chen, *Jun Xing*, Chao Du, Xinyu Huang, Ruigang Yang *IEEE VR 2019*

[10] paGAN: Real-time Avatars Using Dynamic Textures

Koki Nagano, Jaewoo Seo, *Jun Xing*, Lingyu Wei, Zimo Li, Shunsuke Saito, Aviral Agarwal, Jens Fursund, Hao Li SIGGRAPH Asia 2018

[9] HairNet: Single-View Hair Reconstruction using Convolutional Neural Networks

Yi Zhou, Liwen Hu, *Jun Xing*, Weikai Chen, Han-Wei Kung, Xin Tong, Hao Li *ECCV 2018*

[8] Deep Volumetric Video from Very Sparse Multi-View Performance Capture

Zeng Huang, Tianye Li, Weikai Chen, Yajie Zhao, *Jun Xing*, Chloe LeGendre, Linjie Luo, Chongyang Ma, Hao Li *ECCV 2018*

[7] Identity Preserving Face Completion for Large Ocular Region Occlusion

Yajie Zhao, Weikai Chen, *Jun Xing*, Xiaoming Li, Zach Bessinger, Fuchang Liu, Wangmeng Zuo, Ruigang Yang *BMVC 2018*

[6] Autocomplete 3D Sculpting

Mengqi Peng, *Jun Xing*, Li-Yi Wei *SIGGRAPH 2018*

[5] Mesoscopic Facial Geometry Inference using Deep Neural Networks

Loc Huynh, Weikai Chen, Shunsuke Saito, *Jun Xing*, Koki Nagano, Andrew Jones, Hao Li, Paul Debevec *CVPR 2018 (Spotlight)*

[4] Sequence-to-Sequence Learning via Shared Latent Representation

Xu Shen, Xinmei Tian, *Jun Xing*, Yong Rui, Dacheng Tao *AAAI 2018*

[3] Energy-Brushes: Interactive Tools for Illustrating Stylized Elemental Dynamics

Jun Xing, Rubaiat Habib Kazi, Tovi Grossman, Li-Yi Wei, Jos Stam, George Fitzmaurice UIST 2016

[2] Autocomplete Hand-drawn Animations

Jun Xing, Li-Yi Wei, Takaaki Shiratori, and Koji Yatani SIGGRAPH Asia 2015

[1] Autocomplete Painting Repetitions

Jun Xing, Hsiang-Ting Chen and Li-Yi Wei SIGGRAPH Asia 2014

EXHIBITIONS

VR Hair Salon for Avatars

Jun Xing, Liwen Hu, Koki Nagano, Li-Yi Wei, Hao Li. SIGGRAPH 2019 Real-time Live!

Pinscreen Avatars in your Pocket: Mobile paGAN engine and Personalized Gaming

Koki Nagano, Shunsuke Saito, Mclean Goldwhite, Kyle San, Aaron Hong, Liwen Hu, Lingyu Wei, *Jun Xing*, Qingguo Xu, Hanwei Kung, Jiale Kuang, Aviral Agarwal, Erik Castellanos, Jaewoo Seo, Jens Fursund, Hao Li. *SIGGRAPH Asia 2018 Real-time Live!*

Deep Learning-Based Photoreal Avatars for Online Virtual Worlds in iOS

Koki Nagano, Jaewoo Seo, *Jun Xing*, Kyle San, Aaron Hong, Mclean Goldwhite, Jiale Kuang, Aviral Agarwal, Caleb Arthur, Hanwei Kung, Stuti Rastogi, Carrie Sun, Stephen Chen, Jens Fursund, Hao Li. *SIGGRAPH 2018 Real-time Live!*

MEDIA & PRESS

HairBrush for Immersive Data-Driven Hair Modeling

Befores&Afters;

paGAN: Real-time Avatars Using Dynamic Textures

SIGGRAPH Asia 2018 Technica Papers Trailer; fxGuide; LA Times; CBS News; CBC News; Netflix Original and Buzzfeed; Channel One News; Cartoon Brew; NTV (Nippon TV) News;

HairNet: Single-View Hair Reconstruction using Convolutional Neural Networks

Nvidia News; MIT Tech Review;

Autocomplete 3D Sculpting

3Dnchu; MIT Tech Review;

Autocomplete Hand-drawn Animations

WIRED; FastCompany; The Next Web; AnimationWeek; MentalFloss;

CoolThings; TechTimes; 3Dnchu; CGPress;

TECHNICAL REPORTS & PATENTS

Techniques for Generating Dynamic Effects Animations

Pending, US filed by Autodesk (2016), https://patents.justia.com/patent/20180082460

Stroke Operation Prediction for Three-Dimensional Digital Content

Pending, US filed by Adobe (2017), https://patents.justia.com/patent/20180239434

Deep RBFNet: Point Cloud Feature Learning using Radial Basis Functions

Weikai Chen, Xiaoguang Han, Guanbin Li, Chao Chen, *Jun Xing*, Yajie Zhao, Hao Li arXiv:1812.04302.

ACADEMIC SERVICE

Committee Member:

IJCAI 2020

AAAI 2019, 2020

International Conference on Computational Visual Media (CVM) 2019

Pacific Graphics 2018

SIGGRAPH Emerging Technology 2017

Reviewer:

Computer Vision: CVPR; ECCV; ICCV; ACCV; TIP; Computer Graphics: SIGGRAPH Asia; PG; VRST;

Human Computer Interaction: CHI;

PROFESSIONAL SKILLS

Designer:

Neural network, algorithm, system, UI/UX

Programmer:

C/C++, Python/Pytorch, Qt, Java, OpenGL/CV/VR, Unity

REFERENCES

Dr. Li-Yi Wei Adobe Research, lwei@adobe.com
Prof. Hao Li Pinscreen, USC, ICT, hao@hao-li.com
Dr. Rubaiat Habib Kazi Adobe Research, rhabib@adobe.com

Prof. Tovi Grossman University of Toronto, tovi@dgp.toronto.edu

Dr. Jos Stam Nvidia, stam.jos@gmail.com